sigerstudio.eu 2019-04-14

# Privacy Policy – Siger Studio

### PRIVACY POLICY

#### SCOPE OF POLICY

This policy (together with our [Terms And Conditions](https://www.sigerstudio.eu/terms-and-conditions/)) applies to your use of any of our products available through our site SIGER STUDIO (www.sigerstudio.eu) and any of the services accessible through our site.  
In case you are referred to another site, this will be apparent from the address bar in your browser. This privacy statement does not apply to such other sites. In such a case please review the privacy statement on the other site.

This policy sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you or about you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.

##### Controller

SIGER STUDIO  
Regimantas Valiukas  
Murgstr. 18,  
D-76479 Steinmauern,  
Germany

#### DATA COLLECTION

Collecting your data serves to provide you with user-friendly, efficient and secure internet services. We use the collected and processed personal data in order to provide those users who are interested with information.  
Furthermore, we generally process the data with the goal of improving our service and ensuring its security.

No personal data is processed: we process the data anonymously. Whenever you complete transactions using our website, e.g. opening a user account and / or purchasing a product, further data processing processes may take place, of which you will be separately informed.

##### Uses of information we may collect from you

  * Process and use your personal data for research and development, customer administration and support, verifying permitted use of our software and general marketing purposes.
  * Implement security policies and rules to protect personal data under our control from unauthorized access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorized modification and unlawful destruction or accidental loss.
  * Gather information about visitors’ and users’ internet protocol (IP) addresses, media access control (MAC) addresses and email addresses as well as domain names when possible, to detect and reduce abuse by pirates. This is for our protection and yours.  
Use gathered information to determine ways to customize and improve our website, our products and our services to fit the needs of our users.
  * Use cookies to store information about users so that we can remember information to make visiting our website a more personalized and enjoyable experience (see more on cookies below).
  * Use your registered email address to contact you regarding administrative issues with your account.  
Send important information and announcements about us to your registered email address, if you have chosen to opt into the mailing list through your account settings. If at any time you have problems with your settings and/or wish to be removed from this service, please contact us.
  * Process your personal data for the purposes of verifying that your usage of our software is in accordance valid licence terms and (where appropriate) taking action against non-licensed activity.

##### Transmission of data to third parties

We only transmit personal data to a third party to the extent necessary to fulfill our contractual relationship (if at all), if we are bound by law or if it should be necessary in order to implement our general terms and conditions of business or any other agreements concluded with you, or in order to enforce our rights and claims.

In case of institutional contractual partners we will transmit utilization data in aggregated form from is apparent in what manner and to what extent our content is used by the users associated with that institution or company. In such a report we will not transmit any data that can be associated to individual users.  
Provided your personal data is transmitted for other purposes we will ask for your approval in each individual case. If you do not approve we will of course not transmit the data.

#### COOKIES

Cookies are very small text files that are stored on your computer device when you use it to visit many websites. We use cookies to distinguish you from other users, by tracking visitor behavior and storing certain site preferences. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you use or browse the website and also allows us to improve our products, services and the website.

If you prefer not to allow the use of cookies, you can change the configuration of your browser to  
either warn you when you receive a cookie or to automatically reject them. However, you may find that disabling cookies means that certain areas of our site do not function correctly.

If you would like to find out more about cookies, including how to control or delete them, then we recommend you visit [www.aboutcookies.org](https://www.aboutcookies.org/) for detailed guidance.

##### Google Analytics

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies””, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. The IP address will be truncated before transmission. On our behalf Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity and providing other services relating to website activity and internet activity in connection with the use of the website. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser; however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. In addition to that you may prevent the collection of the information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including you IP address) and the processing of this data by Google if you download and install the browser plug-in available at the following [link](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=).

#### SECURITY AND CONFIDENTIALITY OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA

We employ technical and organizational security measures to guarantee that your data is protected from loss, incorrect modifications and unauthorized third-party access. To the greatest extent possible, we ensure that only authorized persons have access to your personal data and only insofar as it is necessary in the scope of the above-mentioned purposes.

#### YOUR RIGHTS

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes and to correct any of your personal data in our possession. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing at any time by contacting us and providing sufficient information for us to identify you and your personal data.

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites and any services that may be accessible through them have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies or for any personal data that may be collected through these websites or services.

#### CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY

This Privacy Policy has been updated in February 2018.  
We reserve the right to amend our Privacy and Cookies policy and any changes we may make in the future will be posted on this page.
